So, as you see on page 16 of the prospectus, the main component of our Northern expansion strategy involves the absorption of the Gerhardt family syndicate, headquartered in Fargo, N.D.
Now the Gerhardts control trucking and distribution for the entire Northern Midwest.
It's a family business, started in 1931 by Dieter Gerhardt.
Now deceased and taken over in 1950 by his son Otto.
Not in the report, but of relevance to this meeting, old Otto had a stroke yesterday on the family compound in North Dakota.
Leaving who in charge?
Unclear.
His wife, Floyd, she's tough, but, you know, a girl.
And then there are the three sons, Dodd, Bear and Rye.
And of course they all want their shot at the throne.
Which the boys in research think provides a tactical opportunity for us to move aggressively to acquire or absorb their operation.
And if you can't, and the current business owners resist,
We liquidate Approved